<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name">Tour@Rome</string>
    <string name="category_attraction">Attraction</string>
    <string name="category_restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="category_gelato">Gelato</string>
    <string name="category_hotel">Hotel</string>
    <string name="detail_price_template"><xliff:g example="$$" id="price">%s</xliff:g> - <xliff:g example="italian" id="style">%s</xliff:g></string>
    <string name="rating_template"><xliff:g example="5.0" id="rating">%s</xliff:g> of 5.0</string>
    <string name="phone_template">Phone: <xliff:g example="+39 123 12312" id="phone">%s</xliff:g></string>
    <string name="address_template">Address: <xliff:g example="adfasdf asfasdf" id="address">%s</xliff:g></string>
    <string name="yelp_label">Yelp</string>


    <string name="detail_label">Top Comment from Yelpers</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_name">Colosseum</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_description">The Colosseum or Coliseum, also known as the Flavian Amphitheatre, is an oval amphitheatre in the centre of the city of Rome, Italy. Built of travertine, tuff, and brick-faced concrete, it is the largest amphitheatre ever built.</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_phone">+39 06 3996 7700</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_address">Piazza del Colosseo, 1, 00184 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_picture">attraction_1_colosseum.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_1_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_name">St. Peter\'s Basilica</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_description">The Papal Basilica of St. Peter in the Vatican, or simply St. Peter\'s Basilica, is an Italian Renaissance church in Vatican City, the papal enclave within the city of Rome.</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_phone">+39 06 6982</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_address">Piazza San Pietro, 00120 Città del Vaticano, Vatican City</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_picture">attraction_2_basilica.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_2_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_name">Trevi Fountain</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_description">The Trevi Fountain is a fountain in the Trevi district in Rome, Italy, designed by Italian architect Nicola Salvi and completed by Giuseppe Pannini.</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_phone">+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_address">Piazza di Trevi, 00187 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_picture">attraction_3_trevi.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_3_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_name">Pantheon</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_description">The Pantheon is a former Roman temple, now a church, in Rome, Italy, on the site of an earlier temple commissioned by Marcus Agrippa during the reign of Augustus. It was completed by the emperor Hadrian and probably dedicated about 126 AD.</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_phone">+39 06 6830 0230</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_address">Piazza della Rotonda, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_picture">attraction_4_pantheon.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_4_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_name">Roman Forum</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_description">The Roman Forum, also known by its Latin name Forum Romanum, is a rectangular forum surrounded by the ruins of several important ancient government buildings at the center of the city of Rome.</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_phone">+39 06 0608</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_address">Via della Salara Vecchia, 5/6, 00186 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_picture">attraction_5_roman_forum.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_5_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_name">Vatican Museums</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_description">The Vatican Museums are Christian and art museums located within the city boundaries of the Vatican City.</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_phone">+39 06 6988 4676</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_address">Viale Vaticano, 00165 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_picture">attraction_6_vatican_museums.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_6_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_name">Castel Sant\'Angelo</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_description">The Mausoleum of Hadrian, usually known as Castel Sant\'Angelo, is a towering cylindrical building in Parco Adriano, Rome, Italy. It was initially commissioned by the Roman Emperor Hadrian as a mausoleum for himself and his family.</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_phone">+39 06 681 9111</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_address">Lungotevere Castello, 50, 00193 Roma RM, Italy</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_picture">attraction_7_castel_sant_angelo.jpg</string>
    <string name="attraction_7_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_name">La Botticella</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_address">Vicolo del Leopardo 39A, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_top_comment">This restaurant is a hidden gem! Just down the street from our hotel (Donna Camilla Sevelli) we were staying in Rome for three nights and loved it so much we had to go back. The owner, Julia, was an amazing host and the staff and service were excellent. We ordered the Zucchini flowers both nights since they were so delicious! I had the clams and muscles, huge portion and the best I\'ve had. My wife ordered a mushroom pasta dish and the second night the cabanara. Both were fantastic. For those people who didn't like the density of the table layout, get over it. Good food at very affordable prices has some compromises. We met the nicest people that all loved the ambiance and the food. We had lunch in one of the "popular tourist plaza's" and got ripped off with wilted salad I wouldn't serve my dog, and paid 3 times as much! This restaurant made our vacation so special, we will be back.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_style">Italian</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_phone">+39 06 5814738</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/la-botticella-roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_picture">restaurant_1_la_botticella.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_name">Sapori e Delizie</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_price">€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_address">Via Giovanni Lanza 102, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_top_comment">This was my first meals once I touched down in Rome and the pizza is so savory and delicious! My brother and I each got one pizza each: Margarita and Prosciutto. Both are very good (we ended up not finishing everything because it\'s pretty filling). The cheese is so chewy and the tomato sauce is so good; I don\'t know what they do differently than from LA pizza places. Also, water cost extra, but everything is very affordable. The restaurant was kind of hard to find at first because it was hidden behind cars. The chefs and employees are so friendly; they were singing and dancing along to the music inside -- loved the environment! It is pretty small inside and it gets busy fast, but totally worth trying! Will go there once more time before I leave.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_style">Pizza</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_phone">+39 06 4875450</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/sapori-e-delizie-roma-2</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_picture">restaurant_2_sapori_e_delizie.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_name">Da Enzo al 29</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_address">Via dei Vascellari 29, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_top_comment">Such amazing food!!! Think this was the best pasta we had in Rome. The Roman classics like amatriciana, cacio e pepe, and carbonara here are SO GOOD. The burrata cheese was also incredible. Try them here! There was a huge lineup when we went. So I would recommend going early around 730 and getting your name on the list right away so you can get seated. Highly recommend!!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_style">Roman</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_phone">+39 06 5812260</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/da-enzo-al-29-roma-2?hrid=fzAXRr22UQqf_NA-ZZNNPw</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_rating">4.7</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_picture">restaurant_3_da_enzo_al_29.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_name">Ai Tre Scalini</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_address">Via Panisperna 251, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_top_comment">One of the most amazing places I have eaten in the world... yes I said world.... The food is unbelievable, service is awesome and the atmosphere is amazing. I Love Ai Tre Scalini.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_style">Wine Bars, Tapas Bars</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_phone">+39 06 48907495</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/ai-tre-scalini-roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_picture">restaurant_4_ai_tre_scalini.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_name">Mamma Angela’s Trattoria</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_address">Via Palestro 53, 00185 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_top_comment">Service was good and price is reasonable. We had monkish with clams, octopus and potato for appetizer and octopus with pasta in spicy tomato sauce. Everything was delish including the wine!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_style">Trattorie, Roman</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_phone">+39 06 48907495</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/mamma-angelas-trattoria-roma-4</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_rating">4.0</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_picture">restaurant_5_mamma_angelas_trattoria.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_name">La Taverna dei Fori Imperiali</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_address">Via della Madonna dei Monti 9, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_top_comment">Loved this darling Italian restaurant! Apparently, the owner has a thing for cats because there were cat references everywhere. Being cat people, we thought this was great. We had a reservation, but had a short wait while our table was readied. The staff were attentive and friendly, even though they were busy. I recommend making a reservation. We ordered several dishes to share. The simple salad was excellent, very fresh and flavorful. My daughter thought the gnocchi we had was the best she\'s ever tasted. I loved the potatoes with rosemary. We both enjoyed the steak we shared. It was tender and flavorful. My only complaint was a little too much gristle on the end of one piece. The bread was fresh and yummy. The rosé wine I had with dinner was good too. For dessert we ordered tiramisu and vanilla ice cream and shared both. I thought the tiramisu was very good, but not great. My impression was the powdered chocolate on top was applied a little too heavy-handed and it overpowered the more subtle coffee flavor, but my daughter really liked it. The ice cream was creamy and delicious. We liked this place so much that, even though there seem to be thousands of restaurants in Rome, we're planning to go back for more before we leave.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_style">Italian, Gluten-Free</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_phone">+39 06 6798643</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/la-taverna-dei-fori-imperiali-roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_rating">4.0</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_picture">restaurant_6_la_taverna_deli_fori_imperiali.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_name">Sette Oche</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_address">Via dei Salumi 36, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_top_comment">Cool spot away from the hustle and bustle of central Rome, close to the River Tiber. Situated in an extremely quiet neighborhood on the edge of Trastevere with indoor and plenty of outdoor seating. Service was solid. We got the Pennette all\'arrabbiata and Spaghetti alla Raffo for lunch. They were both cooked perfectly and tasted great. Also ordered a bruschetta and they brought out some complimentary bread with grilled and marinated toppings (zucchini, olives, potato, mozzarella and salami). I am writing this review from our outdoor table - I didn't want to forget. After coming from Assisi, Montepulciano, Siena and Florence this was hands down the best pasta we've had in the past 10 days after trying REALLY HARD to find great food. We have three more nights in Rome and will be back!</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_style">Pizza, Roman</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_phone">+39 06 5809753</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/sette-oche-roma-2</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="restaurant_7_picture">restaurant_7_sette_oche.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_name">La Prosciutteria - Trevi</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_address">Via della Panetteria 34A, 00187 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_top_comment">So, I visited Rome again and I couldn\'t NOT make this part of my trip. Sure, it\'s a small, crowded little "restaurant" and you\'re seated on stools. But the service is great and welcoming (even for english speakers) and the FOOD is a delicious and aplenty. This stop is easily worth it. I shared a medio tagliere (medium board) with one other person and it came to 20 euro over all. Trust me, it\'s a great value. They give you so much in quantity, quality, and diversity. But they have smaller and bigger boards, depending on your appetite. Even though this location is close to the trevi fountain, it is still kind of tucked away (it's entrance is somewhat small). So, make sure you keep your eyes peeled. Side note for the traveler: they have a DO have self-serve free water (not that finding water in Rome should be difficult).</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_style">Sandwiches, Tuscan, Beer, Wine and Spirits</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_phone">+39 06 6786990</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/la-prosciutteria-trevi-roma-2</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="restaurant_8_picture">restaurant_8_la_prosciutteria_trevi.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_name">Trattoria Vecchia Roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_address">Via Ferruccio 12B, 00185 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_top_comment">Phenomenal pasta with extensive menu. The flambe a pasta is definitely worth a visit. The cheese is melted and infused into the pasta as they toss it in the parmesan or pecorino rinds. We started with salads and moved on to pasta and pizza. The vegetarian pizza was huge! Easily shared between two people and only 8 Euro. The flambe a pasta was also a very large portion, for 9.50 Euro. Our waiter was nice, and able to explain any questions in English. Reservations are a must!!!! There was a huge line of people waiting on the stairs for tables, but with a reservation we were newly seated, greeted, and had a great meal.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_style">Roman, Trattorie, Pizza</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_phone">+39 06 4467143</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/trattoria-vecchia-roma-roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_rating">4.0</string>
    <string name="restaurant_9_picture">restaurant_9_trattoria_vecchia_roma.jpg</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_name">La Casetta a Monti</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_price">€€</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_address">Via della Madonna dei Monti 62, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_top_comment">An adorable little cafe along a romantic, quiet street. Came here as part of my "coffee tour" across Italy. I got, and LOVED, their cappuccino. They produced, in what seemed to be seconds, a perfect little cappuccino with a delicate and delicious foam. Although my experience didn\'t really deviate from the coffee, they seemed to be an affordable cafe all around. The service is curt, but not abrasively so. They give you your space, you'll just need to flag someone down for your check (not an issue at all). For the purposes of a quick stop for a little coffee, I would recommend this cafe. (and don't forget to explore the area and street a little more, this is a great location).</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_style">Italian</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_phone">+39 06 4827756</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/la-casetta-a-monti-roma</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_rating">4.1</string>
    <string name="restaurant_10_picture">restaurant_10_la_casetta_a_monti.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_name">Fatamorgana</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_address">Piazza degli Zingari 5, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_top_comment">A quaint little gelato shop with all kinds of flavors. I tried, their guinia( I think that\'s how you spell it), it tastes like chocolate and hazelnut, sorta like nutella, but better; the wasabi chocolate and the peach mixed with  port wine and raspberry(?). Sorry wasn\'t really paying much attention to the exact ingredients, the amount of ice cream offered a kind of distracted me. So... In the end, we decided on getting.... None of what we tried... Loooool, I\'m sure the gelaterian was like wth... But the flavors we tried just weren\'t all that too my liking, the wasabi chocolate was really weird, it was literally it\'s name, a first punch of wasabi then the chocolate flavors slowly crept up. So anyhow, not going to go into why I didn't choose those flavors....I ended up getting the white almond and dark chocolate. Omg, I was so glad I ditched those previous flavors. These weren't that sweet, and there were little shreds of almond in the white almond ice cream, not to mention these were the none American almonds, which tastes better in dessert. The sweetness from the almonds mixed with the bitterness of the dark chocolate was amazing!  The dark chocolate was real dark, and really good. So to wrap things up, this place is amazing, if I find my way back here, I hope I will be able to come back!</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Gluten-Free</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_phone">+39 06 48906955</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/fatamorgana-roma-3</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="gelato_1_picture">gelato_1_fatamorgana.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_name">Come Il Latte</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_address">Via Silvio Spaventa 26, 00187 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_top_comment">I haven\'t found a gelato place in Rome I didn\'t like and this was no exception! I came here primarily because there was a chocolate fountain. I always appreciate the fact that 1 scoop comes with 2 flavors so I got hazelnut and coffee. I had a hard time deciding and the workers were super patient with me while I mulled around to make my decision. Once I made my choices, they topped it off with a chocolate dipped cookie. The gelato was super flavorful and extremely authentic. It was also really smooth and creamy and the cookie added a really nice crunch. I read somewhere that if the gelato comes out of silver tins with lid, it\'s more legit. Can't verify, but it's legit in my book!</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_phone">+39 06 42903882</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/come-il-latte-roma</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_rating">5.0</string>
    <string name="gelato_2_picture">gelato_2_come_il_latte.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_name">Fior di Luna</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_address">Via della Lungaretta 96, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_top_comment">Phenomenal gelato, among the best I have ever had.  Best pistachio gelato I have ever tasted, and the nocciola/hazelnut was excellent as well.  Not to be missed.</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_style">Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Gelato</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_phone">+39 06 64561314</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/fior-di-luna-roma-2</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="gelato_3_picture">gelato_3_fior_di_luna.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_name">Palazzo del Freddo Giovanni Fassi</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_address">Via Principe Eugenio 65, 00185 Roma, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_top_comment">While visiting Rome with my boyfriend, a bed and breakfast owner told us that Fassi Gelateria has the best gelato, so of course we visited and I can honestly say it was the best gelato I had while visiting both Rome and Florence! Fassi is huge and packed with people! You place your order at one register and bring the receipt to the gelato counter and try to flag down a worker. I got a small gelato cone and it comes with two large scoops and fresh whipped cream! I tried the Caffè and vanilla/Nutella swirl. My boyfriend got the classic vanilla/chocolate. OMG both cheap and delicious!</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_style">Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Gelato</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_phone">+39 06 4464740</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/palazzo-del-freddo-giovanni-fassi-roma-3</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="gelato_4_picture">gelato_4_palazzo_del_freddo_giovanni_fassi.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_name">Gelateria dell’Angeletto</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_address">Via dell Angeletto 15, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_top_comment">With gelaterie a dime-a-dozen in Italy, it really pays to be picky. This unassuming gelateria in the restaurant-rich neighborhood of Monti offere outstanding and great service at reasonable prices. I was most impressed by the owner, who took the time to offer his advice on flavor combinations, since the ones I had chosen were similar to each other. Not the usual "clear the lines" mentality.</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_style">Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Gelato</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_phone">+39 06 4874760</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/gelateria-dellangeletto-roma</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="gelato_5_picture">gelato_5_gelateria_dell_angeletto.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_name">Gelateria Giolitti</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_address">Via dell Angeletto 15, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_top_comment">Ok, I can confirm all the hype around this gelateria is true, this place is da bomb! Forget the flagship store on Via degli Uffici I del Vicario, this one in Testaccio has no queue! I\'ve tried a few famous gelaterias in Italy that are recommended by the locals and so far my favorite is Giolitti!! Hands down the best zabaglione and nocciola!!! With the whipped cream on top they taste amazing! For 3 flavors I only paid €2.30, the super affordable price made me even happier. Must try!! Ottimo gelato a Roma, e spettacolo, non delude mai! Prezzo molto buono, consigliatissimo!!!</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt </string>
    <string name="gelato_6_phone">+39 06 5746006</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/gelateria-giolitti-roma-3</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="gelato_6_picture">gelato_6_gelateria_giolitti.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_name">Gelateria del Viale</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_address">Piazza G G Belli 9F, Roma, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_top_comment">Fantastic gelato. A great selection and top quality. We arrived at the right time. After we ordered a long line suddenly appeared. I had the coffee and raspberry. Great mix. The pistachio was superb as well; probably best mixed with a sweet fruit gelato. Note: my oldest had a big scoop of just the blackberry. It was excellent but ultimately too much of one thing and the accumulated sensation of sugar was too much. Ditto for our youngest who ordered mango and strawberry. Two fruits is just too sweet in a medium bowl. Small cup looks tiny but is the way to go if you\'re just doing fruit.</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt </string>
    <string name="gelato_7_phone">+39 06 5803990</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/gelateria-del-viale-no-title</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_rating">5.0</string>
    <string name="gelato_7_picture">gelato_7_gelateria_del_viale.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_name">Gelateria alla Scala</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_address">Via della Scala 51, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_top_comment">This was easily the best gelato we had in Rome. It is a tiny shop but there is magic in this little nook. Service was always extremely friendly and the price was quite reasonable. My wife tried two or three different flavors. I tried the flavor to top them all: pomegranate and ricotta topped with a pistachio caramel. As evidenced by my reviews, I do not have a sweet tooth. However, I insisted that we visit this place two more times after our first stop. The gelato had the perfect consistency and is in an extremely cool neighborhood that was also amongst our favorites in all of Rome.Get to Trastevere and find this nook of deliciousness.</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt </string>
    <string name="gelato_8_phone">+39 06 6400 3710</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/gelateria-alla-scala-roma</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="gelato_8_picture">gelato_8_gelateria_alla_scala.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_name">Wonderful Ice Cream</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_address">Via Nazionale 19A, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_top_comment">I came here almost every day that I stayed in Rome. This place is amazing. The variations of flavors they have is just amazing and I\'m sure they taste great since the flavors I chose all did. It\'s creamy and rich and smooth. I miss it often now that I'm back home. If I ever have the pleasure of visiting Rome again, this lovely gelato shop will definitely be on my list.</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_style">Gelato, Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Creperies</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_phone">+39 06 4871809</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/wonderful-ice-cream-roma</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="gelato_9_picture">gelato_9_wonderful_ice_cream.jpg</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_name">Gelateria dei Gracchi</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_price">€</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_address">Via dei Gracchi 272, 00192 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_top_comment">Oooo, gelato is delish here.  We tried the pistachio, Micheal Angelo (almonds in an almond cream), strawberry, pineapple, and hazelnut.   All were super creamy and just spectacular.  My taste buds were in awe and thanking my legs for walking past a dozen other gelaterias to get here.   I think they won an award for the Michael Angelo.  I also have to say their cone is the best cone I had in Italy.  Some of the other cones were a bit stale or lacked flavor at the other gelato places, so kudos on a good cone. Point of note: you actually pay at the cashier before you select your gelato flavors.   I'd probably minus a half star because the cashier wasn't so happy when  I brought out my credit card to pay.  Sorry, I'm an American who doesn't like to carry cash or deal with coins.  The points for credit card purchases don't hurt either. Bottom line: the gelato is awesome... this place is worth walking to!!!!</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_style">Ice Cream and Frozen Yogurt, Gelato</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_phone">+39 06 3216668</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/gelateria-dei-gracchi-roma-2</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="gelato_10_picture">gelato_10_gelateria_dei_gracchi.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_name">Palazzo Navona Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_address">Via del Melone 18, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_top_comment">We loved our room at Palazzo Navona - it was modern and elegant.  The location can\'t be beat if you\'re visiting for tourism, because we were able to walk within 20 minutes to almost everything.  There\'s a nice rooftop, but it was too cold for us to use it.  Free breakfast in the morning is pretty good, and the hotel bar seemed nice as well although we did not make use.  I am a fan. What set this hotel apart in my eyes was the free-use smart phone in our room.  You can make calls, use the Internet, look up nearby restaurants, book tours, etc., all through this phone for free.  This was something I didn\'t think would ever be offered by a hotel, so it caught me completely by surprise.  As an international traveler, though, this was an invaluable tool that allowed us to enjoy the trip more by being able to find things quickly without worrying if we were going over our international data limit! The only detractor would be the level of service of the front desk.  They were very nice, but sometimes when we asked questions about things to do, all they had was to give us the tour company brochures.  I'm not sure what concierge service is like otherwise in Italy, but at least coming from the US, at an expensive hotel I expect a bit more.  Ah well, they were good enough that I still give this place 5 stars.</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_phone">+39 06 81152341</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/palazzo-navona-hotel-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_rating">5.0</string>
    <string name="hotel_1_picture">hotel_1_palazzo_navona_hotel.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_name">Hotel Artemide</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_price">€€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_address">Via Nazionale 22, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_top_comment">Awesome staff and amazing rooms. Everything was restocked and cleaned well. Even has a fitness room. The ladies who worked the breakfast each morning were kind and helpful. Thanks guys!</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_phone">+39 06 489911</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-artemide-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="hotel_2_picture">hotel_2_hotel_artemide.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_name">iQ Hotel Roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_address">Via Firenze 8, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_top_comment">The best accommodations!  Convenient location and very friendly staff.  Highly recommend to anyone looking for clean and comfortable accommodations while in Rome!</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_phone">+39 06 4880465</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/iq-hotel-roma-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="hotel_3_picture">hotel_3_iq_hotel_roma.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_name">Hotel Raffaello</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_address">Via Urbana 3, 00184 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_top_comment">This is a great bargain hotel in Rome. It\'s only a 13 minute walk to the Colosseum and Roman forum. It\'s in a cute little art and food district. Be sure to visit the restaurant down the street ( walking towards the Colosseum and across from hotel but down one block) with meatballs and an awesome guy named Max. The hotel is clean, has a great breakfast, friendly staff and very reasonably priced.</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_phone">+39 06 4884342</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-raffaello-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_rating">5.0</string>
    <string name="hotel_4_picture">hotel_4_iq_hotel_raffaello.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_name">Trilussa Palace Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_address">Piazza Ippolito Nievo 25, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_top_comment">We stayed here 5 days and loved it. Convenient, clean, and hospitable staff. Room amenities include free Wi-Fi, cable TV, handy smart phone ( smartphone that lets you make local and international calls for free, you can take it with you during your day trips for directions, reservations etc), US 110v plugs, powerful hair dryer, rooftop bar, spa, gym, safe in the room, clean comfortable beds. Breakfast spread and organic vegetable garden on the terrace is fantastic! Would definitely recommend this place..</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_phone">+39 06 5881963</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/trilussa-palace-hotel-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_5_picture">hotel_5_trilussa_palace_hotel.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_name">Hotel delle Nazioni</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_address">Via Poli, 7, 00187 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_top_comment">I have stayed at this hotel twice. It is in the middle of Rome right near the Trevi Fountain and within walking distance to many other sights like the Colosseum and the Spanish Steps. There are restaurant\'s and more importantly, gellato shops, nearby. The hotel is off of a busy street. We found it to be very quiet. The room was kind of small but the bathroom was very spacious by European standards. The hotel was very clean and immaculately maintained. Complimentary breakfast was included. There was a nice variety of food. The hotel staff was helpful and friendly. We loved it there. I would definitely recommend this hotel for anyone traveling to Rome. You can't beat the location.</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_phone">+39 06 6792441</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-delle-nazioni-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="hotel_6_picture">hotel_6_hotel_delle_nazioni.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_name">Hotel delle Nazioni</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_address">Vicolo del Piede, 2, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_top_comment">Right now I am drinking Proseco under an orange tree.  This is what I envisioned when I pictured experiencing Italy. The Hotel Santa Maria is an oasis! Nestled in the unique neighborhood of Trastevere, the Hotel only has 19 rooms. Our room, Room #21 has 2 beds downstairs and 2 small beds in the loft. Perfect for a family of 4! A large bathroom and ample AC, this room offers you a wonderful stay. The staff is wonderful! So attentive, so friendly.  They will make reservations for dinner, call you a taxi, provide you with a great complimentary breakfast all with a smile and a PREGO! At 5:30 every afternoon, they offer a complimentary Happy Hour, food, not drinks.  After sightseeing all day, it's a perfect chance to unwind until you have your Roman dinner.  I have no idea when I will return to Rome but I will. The Hotel Santa Maria is where I will stay! Bravo!</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_phone">+39 06 5894626</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-santa-maria-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_rating">4.6</string>
    <string name="hotel_7_picture">hotel_7_hotel_santa_maria.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_name">Hotel Navona</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_price">€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_address">Via dei Sediari 8, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_top_comment">This hotel is so beautiful and the staff are so welcoming they assist you all the way to your room, true hospitality! We were able to check in early which wasn\'t a problem at all the front desk gave us a map and explained everything we needed to know about how to get around, this hotel is in the center of it all no need for a car or bike just some tennis shoes... Definitely recommend this beautiful boutique hotel.</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_phone">+39 06 68301252</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-navona-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_rating">4.0</string>
    <string name="hotel_8_picture">hotel_8_hotel_navona.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_name">Hotel Mimosa</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_price">€</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_address">Via di Santa Chiara 61, 00186 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_top_comment">For an America finding this place was a little hard. It does not look like your typical hotel from the outside. It is also a shared space with residential apartments, the hotel does have its separate entrance in the building but the main entrance and the elevator is shared. Once you get past that this place is really really great. The price is amazing for the location. It is in the middle of Rome, easy walking distance to everywhere. Not to mention it is literally right behind the Pantheon. The guys at the desk were incredibly helpful any question we had they were more than happy to answer. You also get free breakfast that isn\'t bad. The room itself is nice and comfortable, nothing fancy but very adequate. I would highly recommend this hotel to any traveler.</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_phone">+39 06 68801753</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/hotel-mimosa-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_rating">4.0</string>
    <string name="hotel_9_picture">hotel_9_hotel_mimosa.jpg</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_name">VOI Donna Camilla Savelli</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_price">€€€</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_address">Via Garibaldi 27, 00153 Rome, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_top_comment">Fabulous hotel and fantastic value. Right in the heart of trastevere, which is the hip and trendy part of Rome. The hotel was converted from a historic convent built on top of a hot spring. It has amazing pieces of art - paintings and sculptures that bring you back hundreds of years in history. Since it was built on a functioning convent, the building has great ventilation and quite cool without too much air conditioning needed. Beautiful and quiet courtyard where breakfast is served. An oasis when we stayed there during the heat of summer in 2015. The service was extremely efficient with super capable and friendly staff. It was the fastest checkin ever in Italy (including a five star hotel in Sorrento). When no one else found tickets to the vatican (including the tour companies with guides), the concierge found them in minutes and booked an amazing private guide for us (Barbara) who also was the private guide for Guiliani. If you book private guide, make sure that you have tickets for both vaticans and coliseums separately. The only downside is the bathroom is pretty small and the door opens right to the edge of toilet and a bit cramped. The drainage of the shower didn\'t work so well. A small downside given the location, historic beauty, and fantastic service.</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_style">Hotels</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_phone">+39 06 588861</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_yelp">https://www.yelp.com/biz/voi-donna-camilla-savelli-roma</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_rating">4.5</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_picture">hotel_10_voi_donna_camilla_savelli.jpg</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
